Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Salute To the International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    By Albert J. Hayes; W. Willard Wirtz; John F. Kennedy; Claude Jodoin; George Meany. Addresses to celebrate the 75th Anniversary of the International Association of Machinists on May 5, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Trade Union Members' Attitudes to Some Current Major Social Questions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    By Albert R. Verri. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union Attitudes Toward University Participation in Labor Education: An Examination and Assessment, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    By Harry R. Blaine; Frederick A. Zeller. Reprint Series No. 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Political Attitudes of West Virginia AFL-CIO Union Members, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    By Keith Dix; Abram Flory. West Virginia University Bulletin Series 71, No. 1-1; Research series 3. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Legal Services as a New Union Benefit, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
    By John A. Grimes. Reprinted from "AFL-CIO American Federationist". Item is in English.
  - Item 2: National Union Benefit Plans 1947-1967, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Labor-Management Services Administration. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Closed Shop in Great Britain, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Jerome L. Toner. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Free Men vs. The Union Closed Shop, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Donald R. Richberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: New Republican Congress Settles Down to Heavy Legislative Program featured: The Question of Outlawing the Closed Shop, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By The Congressional Digest. The Congressional Digest Vol. 26, No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Must Workers Swallow the Closed Shop?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Edward S. Cowdrick. Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Closed Shop - Its Economic Significance and Legal Status, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Thomas J. Anderson, Jr. January 9, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Closed Shop, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Buel W. Patch. Editorial Research Reports Vol. 1, No. 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Closed Shop, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Jerome L. Toner. Statement before the U.S. Senate; CIO Publication No. 151. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Who Wants the Closed Shop?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Russell L. Greenman. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Building and the Public, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Walter Drew. Address delivered at the annual meeting of Associated Employers of Indianapolis on February 16, 1922. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Closed Shop, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 2, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Open or Closed Shop-Which?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Citizens Alliance of Minneapolis. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Closed-Shop Press, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By E. J. McCone. Address to the Illinois Manufacturers Association on October 8, 1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Closed-Shop Press, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Types of Union Recognition in Effect in December 1942, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Memorandum No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Free Men vs. The Union Closed Shop, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By Donald R. Richberg. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    By General Electric. Relations News Letter; April 5, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Policy Resolutions on Community Services, Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the Fifth Annual AFL-CIO National Conference on Community Services, Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Press Looks at Union Power and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Collection of news article. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The ILGWU - Fact and Fiction, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Herbert Hill. A reply to Gus Tyler. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor's Wrongs - and Rights, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By William J. Smith. No. 16 in the Sidney Hillman Reprint Series. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Decline of the AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Frank J. Donner. Address to the UE on August 30, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor at the Crossroads, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Albert A. Blum. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Is Labor Riding for a FALL?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By James F. Lincoln. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: How to Wreck a Labor Union, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Victor Riesel; Aaron Levenstein. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: What the Worker Really Thinks of His Union, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Leonard R. Sayles; George Strauss. Harvard Business Review Vol. 31, No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: How People Make Up Their Minds About Unions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Ross Stagner. Lecture Series No. 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Union Power and Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Selected proceedings from 63rd Annual Congress of American Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Can Union Power Be Curbed?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Edward H. Chamberlin. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Can Union Power Be Curbed?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Edward H. Chamberlin. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A New Philosophy for Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Workers Want Government to Limit Union Power, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By The Wage Earner Forum. The Wage Earner Forum Vol. 59, No. 5; May 18, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Changing Face of Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Milton C. Lightner. Address before the 30th NAM Institute on Industrial Relations on March 10, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Spotlight on Union Activities - Their Impact on Individuals, The Economy and the Public, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Excerpts of proceedings at 62nd Congress of American Industry; December 4-6, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Crisis in American Unionism, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Edwin E. Witte. Address given at the Annual Meeting of the National Academy of Arbitrators on January 31, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Attitude of Union Members Toward Their Union, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Herbert G. Heneman, Jr.; Dale Yoder. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Unionism and the General Wage Level, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Joseph W. Garbarino. American Economic Review Vol. XL, No. 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Unionism and the General Wage Level, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: Unions and Union Leaders of Their Own Choosing, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Clark Kerr. Reprint No. 109. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Where Is Organized Labor Going?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Donald R. Richberg. American Affairs Pamphlets. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Industrial Relations - Frustrated and Perverted, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Emerson P. Schmidt. Address at Conference of Business Economists on September 28, 1946; published on October 17, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Personal Freedom and Labor Policy, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Sylvester Petro. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: How Shall We Deal With Labor Union Monopolies?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Donald R. Richberg. Address delivered before The Economic Club on September 26, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Men and Unions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By John G. Mapes. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Can Labor Clean Its Own House?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: Unions and Union Leaders of Their Own Choosing, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    By Clark Kerr. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Loopholes in the Labor Laws, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The National Economy, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    By AFL-CIO Executive Council. August 23, 1966; Statement by the AFL-CIO Executive Council with a background paper attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Economic Justice: The Needs of Fire Fighters, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    By Stanley H. Ruttenberg; Marvin Friedman. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Economic Programs & Policies for the 60's, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By AFL-CIO, Department of Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Trade Union Organization Work, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By David J. Saposs. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Economic Achievements of the Teamsters Union, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By Robert D. Leiiter. Address before the 15th Annual Shop Conference on Junary 26, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Does Unionism Really Benefit American Labor?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By Allen W. Rucker; N. W. Pickering. No. 18 in a series of Booklet- Editorials. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trade Union Experience and Policy 1914-18 - An Outline, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By Maurice Dobb. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Looks at the Nation's Economy 1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: The Performance of Unionism in Heavy Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By Allen W. Rucker; N. W. Pickering. No. 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Policies for Economic Growth, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    By Walter P. Reuther. Tersimony presented to Congress on February 9, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Strike Situation and Organized Labor's Wage and Job Stategy, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO Resolutions on Education, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Crusade for Public Schools, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
    By John D. Connors. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Steelworkers' Institutes of the University of Kansas, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
    By Frank T. Stockton. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Labor's Library, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By AFL, Workers Education Bureau. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Truth Crushes Commie Lies, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Second Summer Institute, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: New Jersey State Federation of Labor (AFL) Summer School, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By Rutgers University. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Second Annual Summer Institute, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: First Summer School, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Conference on Labor, The Community and Political Education, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Labor in the National Emergency, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By Rutgers University. Hudons Shore Labor School Fourth Annual Training Session in Workers' Education Methods. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Case Studies in Union-University Workers' Education in Three States, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By Herman Erickson; John J. Glynn; Irvine L.H. Kerrison. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Potentialities of Radio in Labor Education, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By William G. Harley. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Workers' Education Material, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By University of Illinois, Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations. Bibliography; List no. 1; May 24, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Workers' Education Material, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By University of Illinois, Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations. Bibliography; List no. 2; October 6, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Workers' Education Material, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    By University of Illinois, Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations. Bibliography; List no. 3; February 20, 1951. Item is in English.
- Box 12, Folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Organized Labor and the Metropolitan Collegiate School of Business, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Mark Starr. Address by Starr on May 24, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: For White-Collar Workers, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Orlie Pell. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Workers' Education: What? Why? How? (What It Is), Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By John D. Connors. No. 1 in a series of mid-monthly articles on Workers' Education; July 15, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Workers' Education: What? Why? How? (The Government Takes a Hand), Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By John D. Connors. No. 5 in a series of mid- monthly articles on Workers' Education; November 15, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Workers' Education: What? Why? How? (How It's Done), Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By John D. Connors. No. 6 in a series on Workers' Education; December 15, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Notebook United Steelworkers of America Labor Institute Summer 1949, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Indiana University. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Apprentice Training in Worker Education Methods, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Hudson Shore Labor School. Report; August 15-28, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Miscellanneous Material on Education of Southern Union Leaders, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Highlander Folk School. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Unions and the Community, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Education Unlimited: A Handbook on Union Education in the South, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Mary Lawrance. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Forging Ahead with LEA: Masters of Our Fate Through Unions of Our Choosing, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By Labor Education Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor Looks at Education, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: 1926-1943 Yearbook of Workers' Education, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    By American Labor Education Service. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Concerning Workers' Education, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By U.S. Federal Emergency Relief Administration. "Concerning Workers' Education" Vol. 1, No. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annotated List of Labor Plays, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Workers' Education - CIO Model, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Summary of Discussions of Study Group on Workers' Education Ann Arbor, July 7-11, 1941, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By New Education Fellowship Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Workers Educational Institute, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Workers Educational Bureau of America. Itinerary for lecture/meeting held on August 27-29, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Workers' Education Today, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Philosophy of Workers' Education, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Labor Unions Educate Against Racial Discrimination; for Political Action and Social Responsibility, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Education That Changes Lives, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Affiliated Schools for Workers. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor Learns Through Action, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Affiliated Schools for Workers. Minutes of Conference of Teachers in Workers' Education on February 18 and 19, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: What Your Union Means, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Alfred Baker Lewis. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Workers' Education 1900-1940, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Labor, Education and Democracy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Irwin K. Kuenzli. Address before the Wisconsin State Federation of Labor Convention on August 18 ,1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Workers' Education in the United States, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Eleanor G. Corr; Mark Starr. Series No. R. 962. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Workers' Education in a Troubled World, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Labor Unions and the Community, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Understanding Basic Problems, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Workers' Education - The Dream and the Reality, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: The ABC of Parliamentary Law, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By August Claessens; Rebecca Jarvis. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Books for Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Workers Education Bureau. A list of publications ofr the Workers Education Bureau of America; No. 41. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Books for Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Workers Education Bureau. A list of publications for the Workers Education Bureau of America; No. 42. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Is This an Imperialist War?, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Harold J. Laski. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Hiring Halls as an Issue in Labor-Management Relations and National Labor Policy: An Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By John B. Parrish; Robert Carson. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: To Clear the Record, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By AFL-CIO. AFL-CIO Executive Counil Reporton the disaffiliation of the UAW. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Two Reponses to the NEA, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By Thomas Y. Hobart, Jr.; Antonia Cortese. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor's Battle with Itself, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By Jerry Wurf. The Washington Post "Outlook" editorials/columnists; October 14, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Facts of the Controversy about the Resilient Floor Workers' Union in Toronto, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Correspondence and newspaper clipping attached to the pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Pulp and Paper Rebellion: A New Pacific Coast Union, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By Paul L. Kleinsorge; William C. Kerby. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Canadian Unions Eye Split With U.S. Parents, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By Neil Gilbride; Joanna Gilbride. April 7, 1974; newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Clarifying Statement Regarding Resignations by UAW Officers From AFL-CIO Posts Pursuant to Instruction by IEB, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By UAW. UAW Administrative Letter Vol. 19, No. 1, February 8, 1967; UAW Administrative Letter Vol. 18, No. 16 attached. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Text of the AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Union Fratricide: The Textile Workers Split, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By Frank T. de Vyver. Reprinted from The South Atlantic Quarterly Vol. LXII, No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Break Between the AFL and CIO, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By John C. Cort. From "The Commonweal" Vol. LIV, No. 25; September 28, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Text of the AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Regional Analysis of Local Union Financial Structures, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By Leon Applebaum. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Dues and Fees Structure of Local Unions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: American Unions and Their Wealth, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By Leo Troy. "A Journal of Economy & Society" Vol. 14, No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Financial Survey of the Major National and International Unions of the United States, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Union Initation Fees, Dues and Per Capita Tax / National Union Strike Benefits, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By Edward R. Curtin. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: American Labor Unions: Political Values and Financial Structure, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By Dan C. Heldman. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Guide for Filling Out the Short Financial Report, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports. Technical Assistance Aid No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Guide for Reporting Your Union Finances, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports. Technical Assistance Aid No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Unioin Financial Statistics 1959-1960\, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Union Dues, Initiation Fees, Per Capita Taxes, Per Capita Revenue and Membership Reported by 150 Unions in 1961, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Bill Analysis: Disclosure of Union Finances, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By American Enterprise Association. 85th Congress - Second Session; Report No. 10; June 10, 1958. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor Partnership in Industrial Enterprise, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
    By Alexander S. Lipsett. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Federal Preemption in the Field of Labor-Management Relations: A Bibliograhy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Suits Against Labor Unions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    By William R. McIntyre. "Editorial Research Reports" Vol. II, No. 2; July 9, 1958. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions, Labor Compensation and Development (1955-1964), Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Morton Stelcner; Sidney C. Sufrin. Reprinted from "Rivista Internazionale di Scienze Economiche e Commerciali" Vol. XVII, No. 2. Item is in English; Italian.
  - Item 2: Embattled Educators: A Brief History - Discussion Guide for AFT Members, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Hawaii Federation of College Teachers. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trade Unions in the United States, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Mary R. Heslet. References to Books on the Histories of Individual Trade Unions in the United States; July 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Little Bit of UE History You Should Know, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Albert J. Fitzgerald; James J. Matles. Remarks to the 33rd UE International Convention on September 9-13, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Kept Ahead of the Future, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unionism Reappraised From Classical Unionism to Union Establishment, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
    By Goetz Briefs. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Making and Shaping of Unionism in the Pulp and Paper Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
    By James A. Gross. February 26, 1965. Item is in English.
- Box 13, Folder (Box 13, Folder 12)